How to connect with CloseSight
First, you need to log in to CloseSight account in CloseSight.
Open the CloseSight app and click on CloseTool庫 in the upper right corner.
Or press the Y button to open CloseTool庫.
In the option card on the top of the tool庫, switch to CloseSight.
Click on Log in and jump to the CloseSight Login page.
Enter your CloseSight account and password.
Click on Log in and close the page.
Go back to the CloseTool app and check the CloseSight assets in the tool庫 window.
The way the tool庫 is operated is similar to the page.
In the left-hand layer, you can switch to different groups.
In the layer bar, select the corresponding workspace.
Double-click to open the selected file.
After opening, we can close the tool庫.
Click on the X or press the shortcut key to close it.
In CloseTool,
we can change the design of the clothing.
After the design is complete, open the tool庫.
Find the appropriate fabric from the CloseSight company resource library.
Double-click to download.
Apply the fabric to the clothing.
Open the tool庫.
In the option card on the top of the tool庫, select Connect.
In the left-hand selection bar, select virtual model.
Here we can change the model's shoes, hairstyle, etc.
Select the type of hair.
Select gender and age as female.
The compatibility is clone female.
The price is free.
After finding the appropriate material, double-click to change the model's hairstyle.
Now switch the type to shoes.
Other settings remain unchanged.
Double-click to change model shoes.
Switch the type to posture.
Other settings remain unchanged.
Double-click to change model posture.
In the left-hand selection bar, switch from virtual model to scene.
The price is still free.
Double-click to increase the scene.
After completion, close the tool庫.
When all the files are completed,
upload this file to CloseSight.
In the main menu, select CloseSight.
You can choose to upload new content or a new version.
In the CloseSight web page, you can choose different groups.
Choose an hour or two.
Select Workroom, and click Next to finish uploading.
If you have other content to watch,
choose YouTube, YouTube Live, or PodCast.
choose YouTube Live, or PodCast.
Click Next and wait until the end.
Click Next to see the uploaded video.